<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>neCo Translation</title>
      <link>http://neco2.github.io</link>
      <description>Blog Posts</description>
      <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
      <generator>a wet piece of cardboard stapled to dying chicken</generator>
      <language>en</language>
      <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 10:33:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
      
        <item>
          <title>Picking up Mangaka-sensei to Zashiki Warashi</title>
          <link>http://neco2.github.io/blog/Picking-up-Mangaka-sensei-to-Zashiki-Warashi</link>
          <description>A cute &lt;span class=&quot;spoiler&quot;&gt;love&lt;/span&gt; story of a scruffy mangaka and a
little zashiki warashi.&lt;br&gt;
Expected release frequency: One chapter per two weeks.&lt;br&gt;
Dumps: Saturday or Sunday around 5pm CET on /a/.
</description>
        </item>
      
        <item>
          <title>About this Blog</title>
          <link>http://neco2.github.io/blog/About-this-blog</link>
          <description>After &lt;a href=&quot;https://mycropen.github.io&quot;&gt;anon&lt;/a&gt; in the scanlation thread
mentioned he was generating a static site from just one text file, I was
intrigued &lt;span class=&quot;spoiler&quot;&gt;mostly because the wiki I set up as an archive
on fandom kicked me out for inactivity&lt;/span&gt; and tried to build something of
my own. He was generous enough to give me his code, which was a great help.&lt;br&gt;
This weird blog/wiki-ish hybrid thing was built using a combination of a lacking
understanding of html, python and &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;,
a static site generator. Similarly to what anon made, this site is generated
from one central YAML data file containing information about the entries
I want displayed on the page, and a couple Jekyll templates.&lt;br&gt;
This is also the first time I&apos;ve built a website, so if you want to keep your
sanity, I recommend you don&apos;t look at any of the html. It&apos;s an absolute mess.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
In conclusion, I put in way too much work into a website that at most 2 people will use per year. But it&apos;s my website, damn it!&lt;br&gt;
If you want to have a look at the inner workings, I&apos;d be happy to share the source with you. Just throw me a mail and
I&apos;ll probably notice within a couple weeks.
</description>
        </item>
      
   </channel>
</rss>
