<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>neCo Translation - Blog Posts</title>
      <link>https://neco2.github.io</link>
      <description>Blog Posts</description>
      <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
      <generator>a wet piece of cardboard stapled to dying chicken</generator>
      <language>en</language>
      <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 08:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      
  <item>
    <title>Shinmusu Chapter 9 Delay</title>
    <pubDate>2024-11-06 16:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/Shinmusu-Delayed</link>
    <description>Chapter 9 of Shinyuu no Musume ni Semarare Komatteimasu will be delayed by two to three weeks.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Changed Download Links</title>
    <pubDate>2024-09-02 12:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/Update-to-Download-Links</link>
    <description>I&apos;ve switched all download links over to catbox. If anyone has set up auto downloads with the RSS feeds, this broke it.&lt;br /&gt;
The feed might spam new entries too, but this will only happen once. I apologize for the inconvenience.
</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Completed Ningyou no Asa</title>
    <pubDate>2024-03-24 06:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/Completed-Ningyou-no-Asa</link>
    <description>The story of Ningyou no Asa currently ends with the second volume at 10.5 chapters.
While it is never explicitly stated that the manga has been dropped, and chapter 10
even has the usual &quot;To be continued&quot;, I belive it to be very unlikely that it&apos;s ever
going to be continued.&lt;br&gt;
But it looks like the author is still alive at least (see &lt;a target=&quot;_self&quot; href=&quot;/blog/Ningyou no Asa Author Still Alive&quot;&gt;
previous post&lt;/a&gt;). I&apos;ll try to keep up with him, and if he ever starts something
interesting again, or if he actually continues this manga, I&apos;ll make a post here.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
But this is it for now. Consider buying the &lt;a target=&quot;_self&quot; href=&quot;https://www.dlsite.com/comic/work/=/product_id/BJ152506.html&quot;&gt;manga&lt;/a&gt;, or the
&lt;a target=&quot;_self&quot; href=&quot;https://www.dlsite.com/home/circle/profile/=/maker_id/RG17989.html&quot;&gt;
  author&apos;s doujin works&lt;/a&gt; on DLsite.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;spoiler&gt;Remember when I thought I could get this done in less than half a year?&lt;/spoiler&gt;
</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Ningyou no Asa Author Still Alive</title>
    <pubDate>2024-02-28 12:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/Ningyou-no-Asa-Author-not-Dead</link>
    <description>Looks like the author is still alive! Earlier this February, he added &lt;a target=&quot;_self&quot; href=&quot;https://www.dlsite.com/comic/work/=/product_id/BJ01214555.html&quot;&gt;
a tankobon version of anata wa neko desu ka&lt;/a&gt; to DLsite. &lt;b&gt;Buy it.&lt;/b&gt; It&apos;s a
doujin series he previously worked on. It appears to just be a re-release
of the old chapters, and there&apos;s no news on NnA, but I&apos;m just glad to know he&apos;s
still around.
</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Hiatus until mid-February?</title>
    <pubDate>2023-11-02 13:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/Hiatus-until-mid-February</link>
    <description>I&apos;m going to be really busy the next couple months. I should hopefully be able to get
back to working on scanlation mid to late February. Until then, everything&apos;s on
hold.&lt;br&gt;
Except the vampire manga since that&apos;s nearly finished and I&apos;m not doing
the typesetting myself.&lt;br&gt;
</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>2023-09-02 Dump Delayed for 3 weeks</title>
    <pubDate>2023-08-12 16:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/Next-Dump-Delayed</link>
    <description>Taking a 3 week break. Work will resume on the second of September,
and the next planned dump will be on the 23rd of September.&lt;br&gt;
Until then I can hopefully manage to come up with a way to deal with the technical
difficulties I&apos;ve been having the past month or two.
</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Picking up Ningyou no Asa</title>
    <pubDate>2023-05-04 17:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/Picking-up-Ningyou-no-Asa</link>
    <description>Would you a stray onaho?&lt;br&gt;
Expected release frequency: Fuck, I don&apos;t know. Life&apos;s going to be getting busy
soon. One chapter every month? Maybe more frequently? I don&apos;t know how much work
this is going to take yet. We&apos;ll see.&lt;br&gt;
Dumps: Saturday or Sunday around 5pm CET on /a/.
</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Completed Mangaka-sensei to Zashiki Warashi</title>
    <pubDate>2023-04-02 06:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/Completed-Mangaka-sensei-to-Zashiki-Warashi</link>
    <description>Chapter 29 marks the end of this manga. I hope you enjoyed, and please consider supporting Nukku. All relevant links can be found on the manga’s page.&lt;br&gt;
I will translate the extra chapters, but I will not stick to a schedule. They’ll be done when they’re done. Please consider purchasing the extra chapters on booth.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Some fun stats about the scanlation:
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Including no-text pages (covers etc.), this manga was 624 pages long&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The project source files total to about 2.7GB of data&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Around 3600 speech balloons were translated, for an average of ~124 balloons per chapter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>(Closed) neCo is currently accepting suggestions for a new scanlation project</title>
    <pubDate>2023-02-01 13:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/neCo-is-currently-accepting-suggestions-for-a-new-scanlation-project</link>
    <description>With the translation Mangaka-sensei to Zashiki Warashi slowly coming to a close, I should decide on my next project soon. If you&apos;ve got any suggestions,
&lt;a target=&quot;_self&quot; href=&quot;/suggestions&quot;&gt;please click here for details&lt;/a&gt;.
</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Mangaka-sensei to Zashiki Warashi Chapter 21 Delayed by Two Weeks</title>
    <pubDate>2022-10-27 21:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/Mangaka-sensei-to-Zashiki-Warashi-Chapter-21-Delay</link>
    <description>Release of chapter 21 of Mangaka-sensei to Zashiki Warashi will be delayed by two
weeks. I need a short break.&lt;br&gt;
The next dump is scheduled for Saturday, the 26th of November. Release on Mangadex
and here the Sunday or Monday after.
</description>
  </item>


   </channel>
</rss>
