<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>neCo Translation - Blog Posts</title>
      <link>https://neco2.github.io</link>
      <description>Blog Posts</description>
      <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
      <generator>a wet piece of cardboard stapled to dying chicken</generator>
      <language>en</language>
      <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 14:13:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      
  <item>
    <title>Mangaka-sensei to Zashiki Warashi Chapter 21 Delayed by Two Weeks</title>
    <pubDate>2022-10-27 21:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/Mangaka-sensei-to-Zashiki-Warashi-Chapter-21-Delay</link>
    <description>Release of chapter 21 of Mangaka-sensei to Zashiki Warashi will be delayed by two
weeks. I need a short break.&lt;br&gt;
The next dump is scheduled for Saturday, the 26th of November. Release on Mangadex
and here the Sunday or Monday after.
</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Mangaka-sensei to Zashiki Warashi Chapter 13 Delay</title>
    <pubDate>2022-06-25 17:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/Mangaka-sensei-to-Zashiki-Warashi-Chapter-13-Delay</link>
    <description>Chapter 13 of Mangaka-sensei to Zashiki Warashi will be delayed by two weeks.&lt;br&gt;
The next dump is scheduled for the 23rd, and the release on Mangadex and here for
the 24th or 25th of July.
</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Picking up Mangaka-sensei to Zashiki Warashi</title>
    <pubDate>2022-02-12 08:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/Picking-up-Mangaka-sensei-to-Zashiki-Warashi</link>
    <description>A cute &lt;span class=&quot;spoiler&quot;&gt;love&lt;/span&gt; story of a scruffy mangaka and a
little zashiki warashi.&lt;br&gt;
Expected release frequency: One chapter per two weeks.&lt;br&gt;
Dumps: Saturday or Sunday around 5pm CET on /a/.
</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>About this Blog</title>
    <pubDate>2022-02-07 10:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
    <link>https://neco2.github.io/blog/About-this-blog</link>
    <description>After anon in the scanlation thread
mentioned he was generating &lt;a href=&quot;https://mycropen.github.io&quot;&gt;a static site&lt;/a&gt;
from just one text file and hosting it on github, I was intrigued
&lt;span class=&quot;spoiler&quot;&gt;mostly because the wiki I set up as an archive on fandom
kicked me out for inactivity&lt;/span&gt; and tried to build something of my own.
He was generous enough to give me his code, which was a great help.&lt;br&gt;
This weird blog/wiki-ish hybrid thing was built using a combination of a lacking
understanding of html, python and &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;,
a static site generator. Similarly to what anon made, this site is generated
from one central YAML data file containing information about the entries
I want displayed on the page, and a couple Jekyll templates.&lt;br&gt;
This is also the first time I&apos;ve built a website, so if you want to keep your
sanity, I recommend you don&apos;t look at any of the html. It&apos;s an absolute mess.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
In conclusion, I put way too much work into a website that at most 2 people will
use per year. But it&apos;s my website, damn it!&lt;br&gt;
If you want to have a look at the inner workings, I&apos;d be happy to share the source
with you. Just throw me a mail and I&apos;ll probably notice within a couple weeks.
</description>
  </item>


   </channel>
</rss>
